Peace! Happiness! Smile!
1, 234!
Smile! More teeth!
Don't let the camera
catch you looking bad!
Smile! 1, 2, 3, 4!
Real joy, not just pleasure!
And natural beauty!
This isn’t fake!
Okay, peace! Peace! Peace!
I'm looking for an actress...
...an actress to play a mother.
Old ladies like you...
When you see
movie stars on TV-
- you must dream of becoming one.
- No, I don't.
- Why not?
- You have nothing else to do.
- No, I'm busy.
These women won't agree
to play communists like this.
It might work if we
invite them to your house first...
But if we ask them right here,
they'll be afraid.
People might think
they really are communists.
I disagree... In my neighborhood
everybody would do it.
Then let's go there instead.
It's impossible here.